picselate.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy – Picselate

The privacy of our visitors is important to us.

At Picselate.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit this site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums or personal accounts.

We also use third party advertisements on Picselate.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This  
could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Google, as a third party vendor, and an ad provider for Picselate.com, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
